vaping.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy - vaping.com

VAPING DOTCOM, LTD.

Privacy Policy

Last modified: June 22, 2016

## 1\.    Introduction

Vaping Dotcom Ltd.  ( **"Company"** or **  "we"**) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through its compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website ‘vaping.com’ (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party (including our distributors, affiliates and subsidiaries); or
  * any third party (including our distributors, affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.

## 2\.    Users Under the Age of 18

Our Website is not intended for users under 18 years of age or legal smoking age. No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from users under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features, do not register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a user under 18, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a user under 18, please contact us at support@vaping.com.

## 3\.    Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, social security number or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("personal information");
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.

## 4\.    Information You Provide to Us.

The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our newsletter, or requesting further online services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including e-mail addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You will be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.
  * Your search queries on the Website.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, "posted") on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, "User Contributions"). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

## 5\.    Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including:

  *  Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.
  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We may collect personal Information automatically, and we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

## 6\.    Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services . They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content or about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising, you should contact the responsible provider directly. 

## 7\.    How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information or products that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products we offer or provide through it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this privacy policy.

We may also use your information to contact you about goods that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data. You can also always opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to support@vaping.com.

## 8\.    Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our distributors, subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the assets of Vaping Dotcom Ltd., whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Vaping Dotcom Ltd. about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To trusted third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [terms of use](https://vaping.com/terms/) or [terms of sale](https://vaping.com/terms-of-sale/) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Vaping Dotcom Ltd., our customers or others (including without limitation distributors, affiliates and subsidiaries of the Company).

## 9\.    Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote products, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data. You can also always opt-out by logging into the Website and adjusting your user preferences in your account profile or by sending us an e-mail stating your request to support@vaping.com

## 10\.    Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into your account profile on the Website.

You may also send us an e-mail to support@vaping.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [terms of use](https://vaping.com/terms/).

## 11\.    Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@vaping.com.

## 12\.    Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Please be aware though that the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites which our Website contains links to or with respect to any third party websites from whom you are directed to our Website.

## 13\.    Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. It is our policy to post any changes on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address specified in your account. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## 14\.    Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: support@vaping.com
